

Contact

•

0404 652 859



wolfgang.stueckle@gmail.com



Melbourne, VIC



Portfolio Page



<u>Github</u>



Linkedin

Key Skills

- C/C++
- HTML/CSS
- Python
- JavaScript
- React
- Node/Express
- MongoDB
- Flask/SQL

Non Technical Skills

- Software project management
- Leading and training of apprentices
- Raising my 2 children as a single dad
- Time management

Wolfgang Stueckle

Software Engineer

I am a seasoned professional with expertise in software development, project management, and electrical engineering. I worked for 12 years at Robert Bosch in Germany and Australia, developing software for engine control systems and addressing production issues. I hold a Bsc in Electrical and Electronics Engineering and a higher diploma in IT from the Academy of Information Technology/Coder Academy. My aspirations are to enhance my skills in embedded systems programming and Al.

Experience

2000 - 2006

Robert Bosch Germany and Australia

Project management and Software development engineer

- Delivered engine controller software projects within budget and timing.
- Specialized in engine control software development.
- Expertise in series introduction for production for Projects of Holden and Suzuki in C and Assem bler.

2007 - 2012

Robert Bosch Pty Ltd, Melbourne, Australia

Production and test engineer

- Found root causes of production issues and implemented actions to avoid re occurrences, improved final test equipment, cycle time and yield rate.
- Specialized in new product introduction (NPI), production release of test stations and software.
- Expertise in test and release of software for final testers in C.

2012 - 2022

Wolf Electrical

Business Owner

- · Planned and installed solar PV systems.
- Specialized in data cabling, and smart wiring.
- Expertise in fault finding, debugging control circuits, and mentoring and training apprentices at various skill levels.

Education and Qualification

1996 - 1999

HSR or University of Applied Sciences Rapperswil/ Switzerland **Bsc in electrical and electronics engineering**

Final Project: Photovoltaic power supply and controller for a circulation pump in a low flow solar heater.

2023

Academy of information technology/ Coder Academy

Higher diploma of Information Technology

 $Projects: \underline{TaskTitan}, \underline{WeatherClock}, \underline{ProfilePage}, \underline{FittAPI}, \underline{Investment\ Calculator}$

2023

UDACITY

Diploma in C/C++

Final Project: Microcontroller for an embedded system

2012

Holmesglen TAFE, Melbourne

Certificate IV in Electrical- Photovoltaic Systems